OK, let's talk about Windows.
好的 我们来聊聊 Windows
If you're using a Mac or Linux or some other Unix-based
如果你使用的是 Mac 或 Linux 或其他基于 Unix
system, you can just skip this page completely.
的系统 你完全可以跳过此页
Just go on to the next page.
直接跳至下一页
Great.
好的
So everyone who's watching, you're on Windows, right?
所以观看此视频的你们都是使用 Windows 的 对吧？
Cool.
很好
So what we want to do for you now
现在我们首先要做的
is to get you a Unix-style shell.
是帮你安装一个 Unix 风格的 shell
Well, what do I mean by "Unix-style"?
那么 我说的“Unix 风格”是什么意思呢？
Well, I mean it's compatible with the shells used
那就是它兼容 Linux 和其他
on Linux and other Unix-like systems,
类 UNIX 操作系统
which is what the majority of web servers run on.
因为大多数 Web 服务器都是在这些系统上运行
Windows comes from a different lineage of operating systems
Windows 来自不同于 Linux 的操作系统
than Linux, so it takes a little extra effort
血统 因此要多花一点功夫
to get Windows compatible with the rest of the world.
才能使其与其他的系统兼容
But that's OK.
但是没关系
The most popular Unix-style shell for Windows
适用于 Windows 的最受欢迎的 UNIX 风格 shell
is the one that comes with the Git Version Control software.
带有 Git 版本控制软件
It's called Git Bash.
叫做 Git Bash
And to install it, we'll install Git.
要安装它 我们要先安装 Git
So go to git.scm.com and download Git.
那么前往 git.scm.com 并下载 Git
I'm just going to click through this installer.
我点击这个安装程序
Next.
下一步
Sure.
好的
These all sound great.
这些看着都不错
I'll do that.
继续下一步
When I get to this page about adjusting your path
当我到达调整 PATH 环境的这一页
environment, I'm just going to accept the default. Default's
我直接接受默认选择 这里同样
good here, too.
选默认选项
And now it's asking me what terminal emulator
现在它问我要与 Git Bash 一起
I want to use with Git Bash.
使用什么终端模拟器
I'm going to choose the default here as well, which is MinTTY.
同样也选择默认选项 也就是使用 MinTTY
Defaults are good there, too.
选默认项就可以
Just going to wait for that to install.
我们等待安装过程完成
This can take a few minutes, but we're going to speed this up
这会花几分钟时间 但是我们要加速它
so you don't have to watch the whole time.
这样你便不必一直盯着它看
You'll be seeing enough of it on your own computer.
你在自己电脑上操作时会看到全部过程
OK.
好的
We're done.
完成了
And now we have a program called Git Bash.
现在我们有一个名为 Git Bash 的程序
Let's run that.
我们运行它
And here we go a-- terminal window.
就会出现一个终端窗口
Hmm.
嗯
It's a little bit hard to read.
上面的字有点看不清
The font's kind of small.
字号有点小
I'm going to go in here and change that.
我从这里更改它
Ah, much better.
哈 好多了
Great.
很好
Now that that's set up, let's take a look at what we've
设置好后 来看看我们
got going on here.
在这里做了什么